Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 544 records, 1930-2013 IBT0051
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Company Records, Series 3; 0 Linear Feet
  - Correspondence, handbooks, policy information, Series 3 Subseries 1
    - County of Nobles [3/4], 1986; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - County of Nobles [4/4], 1987-1990; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Creamette Company, 1978; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Crouse Cartage Company [1/2], 1982-1983; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Crouse Cartage Company [2/2], 1984-1990; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Crystal Farms, 1992; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Culligan Water Conditioning Company, 1977-1984; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - D.J.W. Cartage [1/2], 1976-1978; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - D.J.W. Cartage [2/2], 1977; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Dahlen Transport, 1980-1982; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Delivery Management Services, 1974; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Distron Division, Burger King Corporation, 1987; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Domino's Pizza Distribution Corporation, 1990; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Driver Power, Incorporated, 1975-1980; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Drivers Service, Incorporated, 1985-1987; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - E.L. Murphy Trucking Company, 1977; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - E.S.B., Incorporated, 1980; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Edgecomb Metals Company, 1984; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Edson Express, 1986; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Elk River Concrete Products Company, undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Emery Air Freight Corporation [1/6], 1975-1983; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Emery Air Freight Corporation [2/6], 1983; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Emery Air Freight Corporation [3/6], 1983; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Emery Air Freight Corporation [4/6], 1983-1984; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Emery Air Freight Corporation [5/6], 1985-1986; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Emery Air Freight Corporation [6/6], 1988-1989; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Fairmont Community Hospital, 1978-1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Farmhand, Incorporated, 1978; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Firestone, 1978-1981; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Freight Consolidation Services, Incorporated, 1987; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Furnco Warehouse, Incorporated, 1977-1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Furnell and Webb Transfer Company, 1976; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - G.M.W., Incorporated, 1979-1982; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Garrett Freight Lines, Incorporated [1/4], 1977-1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Garrett Freight Lines, Incorporated [2/4], 1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Garrett Freight Lines, Incorporated [3/4], 1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Garrett Freight Lines, Incorporated [4/4], 1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Gateway Foods, 1981-1992; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - General Sheet Metal Corporation, 1988; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Genuine Parts Company, 1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Gibson Trucking Company, 1987; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Gerdin Transfer, Incorporated, 1975-1981; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Glendenning Motorways, Incorporated [1/2], 1962-1977; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Glendenning Motorways, Incorporated [2/2], 1977; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Golden Pantry, Incorporated, 1981-1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Goodwill Industries of Minneapolis, Incorporated, 1974; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Grain Land Coop, 1993; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Greif Brothers Corporation, 1973-1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Gurley Nut Company, 1987; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - H. Brooks and Company, 1979-1982; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Hart Motor Express, 1978; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Heartland Food Company [1/2], 1989-1993; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Heartland Food Company [2/2], 1990-1997; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Henry Lambert Trucking Company, 1961-1977; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Hodgman Construction Company, 1964; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Hyman Freightways, Incorporated [1/3], 1978-1980; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Hyman Freightways, Incorporated [2/3], 1980-1986; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Hyman Freightways, Incorporated [3/3], 1986-1987; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - I. Bachall Steel and Supply, 1983; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - I.T.T. Continental Baking Company, 1977; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Indianhead Truck Line, Incorporated, 1988; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Interstate Brands Corporation [1/3], 1988-2002; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Interstate Brands Corporation [2/3], 2002; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Interstate Brands Corporation [3/3], 2006-2012; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - J.H. Foods, 1980-1981; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - J&J Transfer Company, 1979; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Jack Frost, Incorporated, 1973-1976; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Jackpot Junction Casino, 1990-1992; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Janesville Auto Transport Company, 1978-1988; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Jennie-O Foods, 1988-1989; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Jenniges Transfer Company, 1977-1982; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Jerry's Foods, Incorporated, 1979; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - John Sexton and Company, 1977-1978; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Johnson Transfer, Incorporated, 1975-1978; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Joseph T. Ryerson and Son, Incorporated, 1976; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - KNUJ/KXLP, Incorporated, 1984-1986; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - Karp's Twin City Supply, 1978-1979; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - Kato Movers and Storage Company, 2000; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - Kelly Transfer, Incorporated, 1974-1979; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 82, Folder 13)
    - Kenosha Auto Transport Company, 1979-1982; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 82, Folder 14)
    - Key City Oil Company, 1970; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 82, Folder 15)
    - Kilian Truck Line, 1973; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 82, Folder 16)
    - L.C.L. Transit Company, 1966-1967; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 82, Folder 17)
    - L.L. Distribution Systems, Incorporated, 1978; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 82, Folder 18)
    - LaBelle Storage and Moving Company, 1980-1983; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 82, Folder 19)
    - Labor Services Company, 1984-1988; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 82, Folder 20)
    - Landry Transfer, Incorporated, 1978-1986; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Landy Packing Company, 1976-1981; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Larson Warehouse, 1976-1984; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - LaSalle Cartage Company, Incorporated [1/2], 1962-1973; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - LaSalle Cartage Company, Incorporated [2/2], 1976-1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Lewis Truck Line, Incorporated, 1975; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Lindsay Brothers Company, 1976-1986; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Liquid Carbonic Industries Corporation, 1991-1995; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Loomis Courier Service, 1976-1978; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Lovelette Transfer Company, 1977; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Luxton Truck Line, 1985-1989; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - M.F. Bank and Company [1/2], 1984-1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - M.F. Bank and Company [2/2], 1985-1986; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - M&R Paving and Excavating, Incorporated, 1996; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - M.S. Carriers, Incorporated, 1987; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - M.T.S. Company, 1980; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Mackay Envelope Company, 1978-1983; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Maiers Transfer and Storage, 1974-1984; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Main Express Company, 1980-1982; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Marigold Foods, Incorporated [1/2], 1983-1990; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Marigold Foods, Incorporated [2/2], 1992-1998; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - Market Square Development Company, 1982; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - Masonite Corporation Distribution Center, 1979; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Mats, Incorporated, 1987; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - May Company, 1977-1981; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - McKesson Chemical Company, 1979-1983; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Medical Oxygen and Equipment Company, 1987; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Merchants Home Delivery Service Company, 1974; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Merchants Refridgerating Company, 1979-1982; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Metal-Matic, Incorporated, 1974-1988; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Metcalf Moving and Storage Company, 1973-1978; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Metro Produce Distributors, Incorporated, 1986; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Metropolitan Contract Services, Incorporated, 1984-1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Metz Baking Company, 1990-1998; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - Mid-America Dairymen, Incorporated, 1991; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 85, Folder 24)
    - Midland Cooperatives, Incorporated, 1977; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - Midwest Drivers Corporation, 1974-1984; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - Midwest Motor Express, Incorporated, 1987-1988; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - Millie Lacs Hospital and Home, 1988-1989; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 85, Folder 16)
    - Milwaukee Motor Transportation Company, 1979-1984; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 85, Folder 17)
    - Minneapolis Cold Storage, 1976; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 85, Folder 18)
    - Minneapolis Food Distributing Industries, 1981; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 85, Folder 19)
    - Minneapolis Household Goods Movers Association, Incorporated, 1978-1983; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 85, Folder 20)
    - Minneapolis Van and Warehouse Company, 1984-1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 85, Folder 21)
    - Minneopa Concrete Products Company, 1988-1992; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 85, Folder 22)
    - Minnesota Boxed Meat [1/2], 1985-1986; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 85, Folder 23)
    - Minnesota Boxed Meat [2/2], 1986-1991; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Minnesota Express, 1979-1988; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Minnesota-Wisconsin Truck Lines, Incorporated, 1978-1979; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Minter-Weisman Company, 1980-1989; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Modern Express, Incorporated, 1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Mohawk Transfer and Storage Company, 1979-1980; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Montgomery Ward and Company, Incorporated, 1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Morell Transfer, Incorporated, 1979-1986; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - Murphy Delivery Service, Incorporated, 1974-1984; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - Murphy Motor Freight Lines, Incorporated, 1965-1984; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - Murphy Motor Freight, Shamrock Division, 1982-1987; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - Murphy Rigging and Erecting, 1989-1990; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - Murphy Warehouse Company, 1974-1987; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - Musingwear, Incorporated, 1979-1982; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 86, Folder 14)
    - Nash-Finch Company, undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - National Drivers, Incorporated, 1974-1984; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - National Food Stores, Incorporated, 1977-1982; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Neuendorf Transportation Company, 1977-1982; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - New Ulm Concrete Products, Incorporated, 1990-1992; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - New Ulm Freight Lines, Incorporated, 1978-1982; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - New Ulm Wholesale, Incorporated, 1984-1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Norman G. Jensen, Incorporated, 1978-1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - North Star Concrete Company, 1977-1996; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Northern Cargo Association, 1979-1983; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Northland Beverages, Incorporated, 1990; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Northwest National Life, 1992; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - Northwest Transfer and Warehouse, Incorporated, 1979-1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - Northwest Transport Service, Incorporated, 1986-1990; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - OCHS Brick and Tile Company, 1977-2000; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 87, Folder 15)
    - Oak Hills Living Center, Highland Manor [1/8], 1990-1991; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Oak Hills Living Center, Highland Manor [2/8], 1992-1994; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Oak Hills Living Center, Highland Manor [3/8], 1994-1995; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Oak Hills Living Center, Highland Manor [4/8], 1996-1997; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Oak Hills Living Center, Highland Manor [5/8], 1996-1997; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Oak Hills Living Center, Highland Manor [6/8], 1997; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Oak Hills Living Center, Highland Manor [7/8], 1997-1998; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Oak Hills Living Center, Highland Manor [8/8], 1997-1998; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Olund Transfer, Incorporated, 1981; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Olympic Express, Incorporated, 1981; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Onan Corporation, 1981; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Pacific Intermountain Express Company (P.I.E.) [1/8], 1978-1984; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Pacific Intermountain Express Company (P.I.E.) [2/8], 1979-1989; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Pacific Intermountain Express Company (P.I.E.) [3/8], 1981-1990; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Pacific Intermountain Express Company (P.I.E.) [4/8], 1983; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Pacific Intermountain Express Company (P.I.E.) [5/8], 1983; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Pacific Intermountain Express Company (P.I.E.) [6/8], 1984; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Pacific Intermountain Express Company (P.I.E.) [7/8], 1984; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Pacific Intermountain Express Company (P.I.E.) [8/8], 1987; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Pacific Gamble Robinson Company, 1978-1984; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Pazik Enterprises, Incorporated, 1986; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Peavy Company, 1974; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Pennant Food Company, 1999; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Pepsi-Cola, 1983-1996; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Perkins Motor Transport Company, 1962-1965; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Perlman Roque Company (North), 1980-1981; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Pickwick International, Incorporated, 1977; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Pictsweet Frozen Foods, Incorporated, 1992; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Pillsbury Company, 1975-1984; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Poly-Tech Division of U.S. Industries Corporation, 1974-1978; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Pratts Express, 1972-1974; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Preferred Products, Incorporated, 1972-1982; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Prepared Foods International, 1980; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Quality Drivers, undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Quast Transfer, 1987; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Quickie Transport Company, 1968-1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Quinn Transfer Company, 1979-1980; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Rapidways Truck Leasing, 1981; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Raymond Motor Transportation Company, 1961-1976; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Red Owl Stores, Incorporated [1/2], 1976-1982; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - Red Owl Stores, Incorporated [2/2], 1981-1982; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 92, Folder 13)
    - Reliance Trust Company, 1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Ringsby Truck Lines, Incorporated [1/2], 1974; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Ringsby Truck Lines, Incorporated [2/2], 1974-1979; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Roadway Express, Incorporated, 1981-1990; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Rocket Transfer, 1977-1980; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Roma Tool and Plastics, Incorporated, 1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Rosewood Corporation, 1981; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Royal Foods, Incorporated, 1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Ruan Transport, 1977; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - S.A.L. Cartage, 1978; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Salt Creek Freightways [1/2], 1984-1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Salt Creek Freightways [2/2], 1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Schaper Manufacturing Company, 1976; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Schwen's, Incorporated, 1977; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Seeco, Incorporated, 1982; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Security Warehouse, 1975-1976; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Service Ideas, Incorporated, 1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Shari Candies, Incorporated [1/4], 1977-1993; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Shari Candies, Incorporated [2/4], 1993-1999; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Shari Candies, Incorporated [3/4], 2001-2003; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Shari Candies, Incorporated [4/4], 2001-2004; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Silent Knight Security Systems, undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Sioux Valley Ready Mix, Incorporated, 1991; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - Skellet Van and Storage Company, 1974-1980; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Sky and Land Express, 1981-1983; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Smith's Transfer Corporation, 1975-1987; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Space Center, Incorporated, 1979-1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Spartech Plastics, 1990-1998; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - State Distributing Company, Incorporated, 1993-1994; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - St. Luke's Lutheran Home, 1996; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Steel Sales Company, 1974; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Stemm Transfer and Storage Company, 1977-1986; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Sterling Cartage Company, 1974-1987; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Stinar Corporation, 1973-1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - Stokely-Van Camp, Incorporated [1/4], 1964-1968; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - Stokely-Van Camp, Incorporated [2/4], 1968-1969; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - Stokely-Van Camp, Incorporated [3/4], 1970-1971; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Stokely-Van Camp, Incorporated [4/4], 1975-1983; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Sunbelt Industries, 1979; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Super Valu Stores, Incorporated, 1979-1989; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Superior Concrete Block Company, Incorporated, 1986-1998; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Superior Dairies Fresh Milk Company, 1990; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Swift Dairy and Poultry Company, 1975-1976; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Swiftlines, Incorporated, 1980-1988; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Team Central Company, Incorporated, 1974-1986; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Terry Brothers, Incorporated, 1979; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - Texgas Corporation, 1979-1982; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - Toll Company, 1983-1989; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Tolley International Corporation, 1974; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Tooltech, Incorporated, 1981; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Totino's Finer Food, Incorporated, 1973; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Town and Country Foods, 1988; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Transportation Systems International, 1984; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Trucking, Incorporated, 1974-1986; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Twin City Freight, Incorporated, 1979-1984; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Tyson Truck Lines, 1987-1990; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - United Foods, Incorporated/Stokely-Van Camp, Incorporated [1/7], 1976-1982; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - United Foods, Incorporated/Stokely-Van Camp, Incorporated [2/7], 1978-1983; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - United Foods, Incorporated/Stokely-Van Camp, Incorporated [3/7], 1980-1982; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - United Foods, Incorporated/Stokely-Van Camp, Incorporated [4/7], 1985-1987; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - United Foods, Incorporated/Stokely-Van Camp, Incorporated [5/7], 1987; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - United Foods, Incorporated/Stokely-Van Camp, Incorporated [6/7], 1989-1992; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - United Foods, Incorporated/Stokely-Van Camp, Incorporated [7/7], 1990-1992; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - United Van Bus Delivery [1/7], 1972-1977; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - United Van Bus Delivery [2/7], 1975-1981; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - United Van Bus Delivery [3/7], 1977; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - United Van Bus Delivery [4/7], 1978-1980; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 2)